<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fuzzing on chinggg的博客</title><link>https://chinggg.github.io/tags/fuzzing/</link><description>Recent content in Fuzzing on chinggg的博客</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 21:20:48 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chinggg.github.io/tags/fuzzing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fuzzing Evolution: How developers make Bitcoin more secure</title><link>https://chinggg.github.io/post/bitcoin-fuzz/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 21:20:48 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chinggg.github.io/post/bitcoin-fuzz/</guid><description>[WIP] I find the evolution of Bitcoin&amp;rsquo;s fuzzing infrastructure interesting, so I am writing a essay to make a survey of that.
Fuzzing Evolution: How developers make Bitcoin more secure Intro Bitcoin is one of the most prominent distributed software systems in the world, and a key part of a potentially revolutionary new form of decentralized financial (DeFi) tool, cryptocurrency. Due to its distributed nature, Bitcoin in some sense is the sum of the operations of the code executed by many independent nodes rather than the original software created by Satoshi Nakamoto.</description></item><item><title>My Experience in Summer of Bitcoin 2022</title><link>https://chinggg.github.io/post/summer-of-bitcoin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 21:20:48 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://chinggg.github.io/post/summer-of-bitcoin/</guid><description>What is Summer of Bitcoin?
a global, online summer internship program focused on introducing university students to bitcoin open-source development and design
When I started to write my proposal for it, there was only one week to go before the deadline. Luckily, my experience with OSS-Fuzz and my efforts paid off. I am proud to become one of the 83 students who will participate in Summer of Bitcoin 2022 and contribute to Bitcoin Core under the guidance of Marco Falke.</description></item></channel></rss>